bebee.com 2019-12-16

# Privacy Policy | beBee

beBee is a trademark of beBee Affinity Social Network, SL.. CIF: B84471838.

## 1\. Right to Information

If the user decides to register at bebee.com, (hereinafter beBee) we will only request the information strictly necessary to achieve the aims and purposes which the website is intended for.

### Information that beBee receives from users

This refers to information that you enter when registering (required) and all that you choose to share in the various features of the platform (optional information).

**Registration Information**. In order to use the service of bebee it is necessary that you register with your personal information, including your name, email address, date of birth, gender, country and professional sector. **Information Shared by the User**. The information also refers to all actions made by the user as interaction in Bebee, such as buzzes sharing, updates, photos or videos you upload, comments on other buzzes on your wall, joining affinity groups, users and companies you follow and the use of our tool to import contacts from your contacts.

### Public Information

As a professional network where all user profiles are public, beBee aims to provide a service that is as complete as possible, by publishing most of the information provided by users: Name, surname, picture, professional experience, place of residency, academic studies, additional courses and certificates, affiliation to hives, languages, professional skills, links to other profiles and social networks or blogs and contact network. 

All of this information may be available to the public and may be shared by all users of the network and even those who aren’t. If users do not wish for all or part of their information to be public, they may cancel their account or contact our support services to deregister. 

**Indexation in public search engines**

Even though beBee profiles are always public, users have the possibility of choosing whether they want their profiles to appear on public search engines such as google or bing. If they do not, although their profiles remain public, beBee will ensure that they are not registered or indexed by search engines. 

### User’s Private Data

Information provided by users in the private section of their profile is not shown on their public profiles. Therefore, their data cannot be seen by other internet users. Nevertheless, when a user makes a request to subscribe to a job offer, his data is automatically shown to the company offering the position, so that they may assess the candidate and contact him if interested. Data that is considered private includes: Date of birth, email address, phone number, sex, salary, postal address, nationality, work permit, driving license, availability to move or travel and curriculum vitae. 

### Use of user information

Information received from each user is used to provide the services and functionalities in the best way possible for all users, registered companies, partners and advertisers within bebee. The main service that beBee offers is providing truly relevant and related content to each of its members, including suggestions and advertisements posted on each wall, which is aimed specifically at users who really might be interested; this is achieved by knowing the gender, age, profession, geographic location, the interest groups, including data collected before and after registration at bebee.

With the user information bebee can make internal operations, such as data analysis, solving problems, research, development of new tools and service improvement and interface operations.

At no point will beBee share your user information without your concept through the text of the present policies and of your formal acceptance of these. The user who accepts and is in agreement with the conditions presented grants permission for such purposes. The user details are used exclusively by beBee and are not shared with advertisers or with external organizations.

The only exception is in case there should be a change of property management or the sale of a part of the total sale of beBee, they could share the information of the users to a third party, who is entitled to use such information in accordance with the policies in course by bebee and your future changes with previous notice and consent of the user.

The users details are stored for a set period of time required to provide the services and products that bebee offers to them. Generally, the information associated with an active account at bebee is preserved until the conclusion of the definitive unsubscription of the account; the retention of data is only made for certain types of details.

### Services provided by beBee to users

beBee is an affinity social network, connecting like-minded people by their profession and/or areas of interest.

After the registration process and registration for free, beBee offers a range of services and tools for the user based on affinity over a wide range of interests: employment, leisure, education, technology, travel, automotives, dating, e-commerce, etc, all through our online platform of beBee. Within the user profile, beBee offers relevant content based on the interests declared by the user at the time of the subscription and through the behavior observed by their interactions within the site.

As such, bebee suggests all kinds of information and online services, training, networking, affinity groups, jobs, services, notifications, activities and leisure opportunities, tourism, etc. considered to be of interest to the user. For this purpose, it is required that users truthfully and correctly complete the electronic form and the include their personal and professional information necessary for the functions and purposes described. The treatment of user data is focused on achieving these purposes within the regulatory framework.

Data provided by users will be incorporated into a file owned by beBee Affinity Social Network S.L. This file is registered and controlled by the Spanish Data Protection Agency.

### Services provided by beBee to recruiters

  * Posting job offers and / or services on beBee.
  * CV’s. database.
  * Management of the recruitment process
  * Services related to the management of the selection of candidates and other services that beBee considers to be of interest for the companies. Affinity groups, education, contact network, notifications, promotions and offers of third parties
  * Electronic communications service
  * Exclusive tools to use for the Premium (Bee+) account version for recruitment and for users searching for jobs or other purposes.

The personal data of users is stored in a database owned by bebee, registered with the Data Protection Agency. The data collected is adequate, relevant and not excessive in relation to the scope, purpose and specification of the service which is an explicit and legitimate service of beBee. beBee has adopted the necessary technical and organizational measures to ensure the security of personal data and avoid its alteration, loss, or unauthorized access, given the state of technology, the nature of the data stored and the risks to which they are exposed, all in accordance with the provisions of Royal Decree 994/1999 of 11 June and other control procedures for the security of information systems.

## 2\. User Consent

By clicking on the "Create Account" in the Registration form the user gives unambiguous and explicit consent to the processing of personal data in accordance with the purposes and services provided by bebee and, where appropriate, transferable to third parties for service fulfillment (with the conditions specified in the paragraph privacy control). For these purposes “third party entities” using the bebee services means that users authorize beBee to access their personal data, regardless of their level of privacy, in order to inform users of job offers suitable and ideal for the professional profile of the user.

### Electronic communication service

**Alerts:** Receive free automated jobs, services and other opportunities Through bebee electronic communications (email and SMS) are sent for free, quickly, can be personalized and all the necessary information which best suits the interests of the user, among others, email services, (registration, remembering password, invitations, subscription, etc); Alerts by keywords, instant alerts by geographic location, interest and collectively; job bulletin by province and categories; education bulletin by geographic location, interests and collectively. beBee establishes two mechanisms by which users who request to be excluded from this service can proceed easily and for free. To do this, the user must login to bebee and go to your ¨Private Menu¨ located at the top right of your profile, click the 'Alerts' or 'Notifications' section and disable the option to receive this service or configure each as desired. You can exclude yourself from the services by following the instructions which are indicated at the bottom of each email that you receive from beBee.

**Other communications** beBee sends various communication to registered users via (email, sms, web, mail and mobile devices) notifications and advertising related to beBee, the field of recruitment, as well as the sectors of music, television, film, radio, communication, training and education, hospitality, finance, distribution, sports, travel, insurance, NGO, editorial, automotive, employment, property, meteorology, sales, energy, fashion, textiles, video games, health, leisure, management , electronics and telecommunications. bebee sends these to users who previously have authorized the following electronic communications:

  * beBee Newsletters: Tips for finding career opportunities, reports, trends, etc.
  * Sectoral Newsletters: Information on employment in specific sectors.
  * Developments: beBee developments and knowledge about tools and the purposes.
  * Advertisements: Promotion of products and services of third parties.

## 3\. Content posted and shared by the user

### Control of buzzes

Publications, comments and recommendations (relevants) made by the user are always public and shown next to his name and profile picture. This information can be seen by any other user of the internet. 

The user should note that any publication made in the user´s account is the responsibility of the administrative user of that account, and all the content generated becomes part of the property of beBee. After the unsubscription of an account, part of the shared content of the previous dates will continue to be visible on beBee, the author´s name (the user who has unsubscribed) will be replaced by ¨Anonymous¨

### Content and information that a user shares of another user

Tags and links. Any beBee user can include links and tags to their buzzes and updates. The links are understood as URL that direct you to a website and can be both internal or external to beBee. In case a private profile is linked to a post, once clicking the link it is only possible to view the public content mandatory by the profile. A tag is a type of link generally used in mentioning the other user. When a user tags another in a post, the tag links the profile of the user mentioned. In case the user does not want to be tagged by another person, it is recommended to get in contact with the other directly and to tell them. If in the case the person still decides to tag, then the user can block the other so that they can not be tagged.

### Groups

Only the user can decide if you belong to an affinity hive or not, and it is he /she who decides when to leave. When a user belongs to a hive, all buzzes within the hive will be displayed on the wall of the user. You may be mentioned, tagged, linked or added to updates being made by other members in the hive.

The user must keep in mind that all buzzes made within a hive can be read and used by other members; bebee is not responsible for the disclosure of information that is made within these forums or affinity groups. The user can remove any buzzes at any time made to a hive, but it should be noted that other members may be copied in all or part of the information that was once shared.

### Searches

All the users can use the search function at beBee to find other users inside and outside of your hive (professional sector), or to find companies, affinity groups, job offers, keywords, etc.

### Business pages and other instructions (universities, public figures, etc.)

The pages of institutions such as companies, universities and other entities are public at bebee. All information posted and shared through these will be visible to the creator user (member of the institution). All the following users of these pages appear as followers of the page and can be seen both by the owner or by other users.

### Cookies and IPs

The user accepts the use of cookies and IP tracking. Our site traffic analyzer uses cookies and IP tracking that allow us to collect data for statistical purposes: date of first visit, number of times you have visited, date of last visit, URL and domain, browser used and screen resolution. However, users can disable and/or eliminate these cookies following the instructions of your Internet browser.

## 4\. Right of Revocation, Opposition, Access, Correction, Updates and Cancellation of Data

The user has the right to access personal data, rectify if data is incorrect and unsubscribe from beBee´s services. Thus, the user can withdraw their consent at any time for a justified cause, but can not have retroactive effects. These rights can be exercised by the configuration of the website in case of trouble for doing this online. In case you have any problems of completing this online like any other type of query or concern in respect to our privacy policy of data you write by email to _**data-protection@bebee.com**_ or contact via postal mail in the address:

beBee Affinity Social Network S.L.   
Calle de Anabel Segura, 11   
Edificio A, 4D   
28108 Alcobendas - Madrid (Spain)   

bebee fully complies with applicable laws regarding the protection of personal data and privacy commitments of its activity. The processing of personal data and the sending of electronic communication is adjusted to the rules established by the [EU General Data Protection Regulation](https://www.eugdpr.org/), and the spanish Organic Law 15 / 1999.13 December, Protection of Personal Data (BOE 14/12/1999) and Law 34/2002 of July 11 of Information Society Services and Electronic Commerce (BOE 12/07/2002).

**Sending of communication**

In case beBee makes any changes to its policy of the use of data and privacy, they will notify users by posting on this document. In case of relevant or lange changes, the users will be notified with prior notice under the required circumstances.

beBee Affinity Social Network S.L.   
Calle de Anabel Segura, 11   
Edificio A, 4D   
28108 Alcobendas - Madrid (Spain)   
C.I.F B-84471838   
Inscribed with the Madrid Companies Register in Volume 21938, folio 15, section 8, page M-390918, entry 1.
